Going to the gym can be something that many people find a gruelling experience.
去健身房对很多人来说可能是一种折磨人的（gruelling）经历。
It takes time and effort, it often hurts, and it can be extremely tedious.
这需要时间和努力，而且常常会让人感到疼痛，还可能极其无聊（tedious）。
Most weight-related exercises are a combination of sets and reps.
大多数与举重相关的锻炼是组数和次数的结合。
In order to see any significant change from any one exercise, it will probably need to be repeated six to eight times, for a minimum of three sets, for about three months.
为了从任何一项锻炼中看到明显的变化，可能需要重复六到八次，至少做三组，持续大约三个月。
Then there's cardio.
然后还有有氧运动（cardio）。
For some, there's nothing more boring than endless miles spent running on a treadmill.
对有些人来说，没有什么比在跑步机（treadmill）上无休止地跑上数英里更无聊的了。
But what if there were a way to alleviate the boredom of exercise while still getting a good work out?
但是，如果有一种方法可以在仍然进行良好锻炼的同时减轻（alleviate）锻炼的无聊感呢？
Luckily for us, there’s virtual reality.
幸运的是，我们有虚拟现实技术。
In the past, “playing video games was a sedentary experience,” says Jo Stauffer of the VR Health Institute, “but VR changes all of that".
过去，“玩电子游戏是一种久坐不动的（sedentary）体验，”虚拟现实健康研究所（VR Health Institute）的乔・斯托弗（Jo Stauffer）说，“但虚拟现实改变了这一切。”
He says that the room-scale experience engages your body in full.
他说，空间定位体验能让你的身体完全参与（engages）进来。
Many VR games are played while standing.
许多虚拟现实游戏是站着玩的。
In order to play properly, the player is forced to move around swinging their arms or using their legs.
为了玩好游戏，玩家不得不四处移动，挥舞手臂或使用双腿。
After an hour of this on a regular enough basis, it’s not surprising that many people unexpectedly find themselves a little fitter.
如果经常这样玩上一个小时，很多人意外地发现自己更健康一点也就不足为奇了。
There are already a number of virtual reality games which, deliberately or not, result in their player ‘getting a good sweat on’ if played for enough time.
已经有许多虚拟现实游戏，不管是不是有意为之，如果玩的时间足够长，都会让玩家“出一身汗”。
For example, there’s a first person shooter which forces the player to sidestep, duck and dodge incoming projectiles.
例如，有一款第一人称射击游戏，迫使玩家侧步走（sidestep）、弯腰躲避（duck）和闪避（dodge）飞来的投射物。
That’s cardio.
这就是有氧运动。
Or there’s a music game which forces players to shadowbox in order to hit the notes – that’s an upper-body workout.
或者有一款音乐游戏，迫使玩家做空拳训练（shadowbox）以便击中音符——这是一种上半身锻炼。
The potential for VR to help people get fit has been noticed by one company.
虚拟现实帮助人们健身的潜力已经被一家公司注意到了。
They want to take the whole experience into the gym.
他们想把这种体验引入健身房。
They are making a bespoke resistance machine, designed to be used in combination with a VR headset.
他们正在制造一种定制的（bespoke）阻力机器，设计成与虚拟现实头戴设备结合使用。
Players challenge a virtual opponent in a series of games, which results in a 30-minute full-body work out.
玩家在一系列游戏中挑战虚拟对手，这会带来一次30分钟的全身锻炼。
However, the cost of the equipment is expensive and there are safety concerns to be worked out, says J P Gownder from the consultancy Forrester.
然而，咨询公司佛罗斯特咨询公司（Forrester）的J・P・高恩德（J P Gownder）说，设备的成本很高，而且还有一些安全问题需要解决。
So don’t hang up your gym shorts just yet.
所以，先别急着把你的健身短裤收起来。
Although it’s early days, for those of us who struggle to overcome the tedium of exercise, a new solution could be coming.
尽管还为时尚早，但对于我们这些努力克服锻炼乏味感的人来说，一种新的解决方案可能即将到来。
And a world where a person can exercise and have fun at the same time might be something that many people would want – virtual or not.
而且，一个人们可以同时锻炼和享受乐趣的世界可能是许多人所向往的——不管是不是虚拟的。